I'm going to show you how to make a Scrumptious Coffee.
Now what I'm going to make here is a single serving, but you can also make this in a pan over the stove.
Just make sure that when you heat it you don't bring it to a boil.
Now if you're going to make an individual serving you can heat this up in the microwave.
We're going to start off with a very strong hot cup of coffee, and we'll add to that some sugar.
You can also use brown sugar, so that's up to you.
And I like my coffee sweet, like I like my men, so I'm going to add, whatever that means, I'm going to add two tablespoons of sugar, and then I'm going to add in the liquor.
We're going to do a half an ounce of brandy, just like so.
And we're also going to add a half an ounce of dark rum.
And if you decide to do this in a larger pot just increase the amount of your liquor as you would increase the amount of your coffee.
Also, a half an ounce of rum and I'm going to stir that up again.
I'm going to drop in an orange peel, and then I'm going to let this infuse as I heat it in the microwave for about thirty seconds.
Once I take it out I'm going to top it with whip cream.
A little bit of nutmeg, just like so.
And if you would like to add another orange peel on top, feel free to do so.
And there you have it, a Scrumptious Coffee.
Cheers.